clubmonaco.ca 2018-05-13

# Customer Assistance | Club Monaco Canada

Effective Date: March 1, 2012

Club Monaco respects your privacy. Our Privacy Notice describes the types of information we gather online, in our Stores and in other interactions we have with our customers. This Privacy Notice also describes how we use, disclose and otherwise manage this information. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. 

This Privacy Notice may be updated from time to time. Accordingly, you should check the date of this Notice (which appears at the top of this page) and review any changes since the last version. Your continued use of the Site following any modifications demonstrates your agreement to such changes. If at any time you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice, please do not use this Site or provide us with personal information when shopping in our Stores. 

* * *

Club Monaco, or a third-party service provider acting on our behalf (“Service Provider”), may collect and use information from and about you as described below.

### Personal Information

Club Monaco may collect personal information from you in various ways, including when you (1) order or purchase products, gift cards or services from us; (2) register with us on our Site to shop or participate in our online community; (3) sign up for newsletters, emails or other communications from Club Monaco; (4) participate in surveys, contests, sweepstakes or promotions; (5) utilize our Email to a Friend feature; or (6) request information from us or otherwise contact us. The personal information we collect may include your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, payment card information, birthday and gender. 

We use information from and about you: (1) to process and administer payments or returns, provide services and communicate with you about your purchases; (2) to improve your shopping experience and help us target specific products and services to you; (3) to respond to your inquiries; (4) to communicate with you about our products and services; and (5) to help us develop and improve our Site and Stores and tailor our Site and Stores to your interests. 

Additionally, Club Monaco may combine your personal information with personal and nonpersonal information we receive from and about you from other online and offline sources.

### Website-Related Information

Club Monaco may collect additional information from you, including—but not limited to—your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name from which you access the Site and service provider, as well as information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visited the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other Site usage data.

We use this information: (1) to review the usage and operations of our Site and services; (2) to address problems with our Site, our business or our products and services; and (3) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business.

For example, we use a Service Provider to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Site. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve our Site, products, offers or marketing strategy, you can opt out of this Site analysis tool by [clicking here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/product).

### Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a small data file that sites often store on your hard drive when you visit the Site. Club Monaco may place cookies on your computer to collect information about your visit to the Site and to improve Site functionality. For example, we may place cookies on your computer to understand which pages of the Site you’ve visited, determine which areas and features of our Site are most popular, learn how search engine referral is working effectively, provide unique user identification, preserve the contents of your shopping bag between your visits and obtain product browsing and purchasing history. 

You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent, but if you turn off cookies or refuse them, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Site’s features, such as making a purchase on the Site or accessing your registered user account information. 

A web beacon, also known as a clear GIF or pixel tag, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our Site or a third-party site where we may advertise, but not on your computer. When you access these pages, web beacons generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies, the web beacon will simply detect an anonymous site visit. We may also use cookies or web beacons to manage and deliver more relevant advertisements on the Site, across the Internet and via email. To learn more about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by our Service Providers, please [click here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/product). Web beacons may also be used to report certain information (but not your name, address, email address, telephone number or payment information) about your visits to our Site and other sites that advertise and feature links to our Site, in order to measure the effectiveness of our advertisements. Cookies or web beacons may also be used to let us know if you have opened an email from us. This information allows us to make improvements and updates to enhance your experience. 

* * *

Club Monaco does not share, sell or trade your personal information gathered online with third parties, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Notice. Club Monaco also does not contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give third parties access to such personal information. 

We may share your information with our Service Providers that provide internal business, professional or technical-support functions for Club Monaco. Your personal information may be maintained and processed by these Services Providers in Canada. Our Service Providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. For additional information on our Service Providers, contact our Privacy Officer as set out below.

Club Monaco and our Service Providers may share your personal information if such action is required for Club Monaco or any of our Service Providers to comply with any valid legal process, such as a subpoena, search warrant, statute or court order, or any valid administrative or investigative request from a law-enforcement agency. We may also disclose personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims or as otherwise permitted by applicable Canadian law. In addition, we may share your personal information if we or any of our Service Providers believes that such disclosure is necessary to address any unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another customer or of the general public. 

Club Monaco may also share aggregate nonpersonally identifiable or anonymous information about you, such as age, gender, types of products viewed, frequency of Store visits, Site pages you access most frequently or search terms you enter with third parties. For example, Club Monaco may provide a third party with such information as the number of people who shopped at our Site during a specific time period or the number of people who shopped at our Stores and meet certain demographics (e.g., age or gender) during a specific time period. This aggregate nonpersonally identifiable or anonymous information does not personally identify a specific visitor to our Site or Stores.

During the normal course of our business, Club Monaco may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties.

* * *

Protecting your order information is a priority for us. We have taken reasonable physical, administrative and technical steps designed to safeguard the information we collect from and about our customers and Site visitors. For example, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. While we make every effort to help ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures. 

We have personal-information retention processes designed to retain personal information of our customers no longer than necessary for the purposes stated above or to otherwise meet legal requirements. 

* * *

You have the right to access, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may access, update and correct some of your personal information online if you have registered for a Club Monaco Account. Otherwise, you may do so by emailing or writing to us at the contact information set out in the Contact Us section below. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records. 

This Site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. These links are provided solely for the convenience of our Site visitors. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third-party websites or services. 

You can contact our Privacy Officer at:

Chief Privacy Officer  
Club Monaco Corporation  
9 Polito Avenue  
Lyndhurst, NJ 07071 

For access to your personal information or to request removal from any of our marketing lists, please contact:

Senior Director, Database Marketing  
625 Madison Avenue, 7th Floor  
New York, NY 10022 

Please be sure to include in any email or postal mail your full name, email address, postal address and any message. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.
